Hey, thanks for watching.
I hope you've enjoyed taking this course just as much as I've
enjoyed sharing it with you.
Now, I encourage you to continue exploring the world of AI and marketing.
The best thing you can do is to continue investing in your education.
Now, there are a ton of great AI and marketing courses right here.
On the AI front, you might enjoy how to boost your
productivity with AI tools, or even what is generative AI.
Now, if you're looking to uplevel your advertising skills, well,
your next stop might be my course, Google Ads Essential Training.
Or if you're looking to further expand your knowledge on launching digital
marketing campaigns, well, you might enjoy my course, Digital Marketing Foundations.
As always, you can connect with me directly on LinkedIn.
I'd love to hear from you, and have fun, and good luck!